rankstore.com 2015-06-16

# Privacy Policy | RankStore.com

**TABLE OF CONTENTS**

**Collection of your Personal Information**. 2

**Use of your Personal Information**. 2

**Use of Cookies**. 3

**Security of your Personal Information**. 3

**Children Under Thirteen**. 4

**Opt-Out & Unsubscribe**. 4

**Changes to this Statement**. 4

**Contact Information**. 4

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the **rankstore.com** and **New Developments, LLC** and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to **New Developments, LLC** include **rankstore.com** and **RankStore**. The **RankStore** website is a traffic and/or advertising website that provides Alexa traffic boosting. When it comes to choosing a company that can help increase your Alexa ranking, why do you need us by your side? It’s actually quite simple really! When you hire us to improve your traffic ranking, you’re going to get all the experience we have to offer with our proven track record. By using the **RankStore** website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

**RankStore** may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future. If you purchase **RankStore’s** products and services, we and/or PayPal will collect your billing and your credit card information. This information is used to complete the purchase transaction. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by **RankStore**. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the **RankStore** website.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through **RankStore** ‘s public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others.

**RankStore** encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from **RankStore** so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. **RankStore** is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the RankStore website.

**RankStore** collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.

**RankStore** may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from **RankStore** and its affiliates. **RankStore** may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

**RankStore** does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.

**RankStore** may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. **RankStore** may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to **RankStore** , and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

**RankStore** may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within **RankStore** , in order to determine what **RankStore** services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within **RankStore** to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

**RankStore** will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on **RankStore** or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of **RankStore** ; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of **RankStore** , or the public.

The **RankStore** website may use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize **RankStore** pages, or register with **RankStore** site or services, a cookie helps **RankStore** to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same **RankStore** website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the **RankStore** features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the **RankStore** services or websites you visit.

**RankStore** secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure.

All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers.

Access by you to your account is available through a password and/or unique user name selected by you. This password is encrypted. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone, that you change your password often using a combination of letters and numbers, and that you ensure you use a secure web browser. We cannot be held accountable for activities that results from your own neglect to safeguard the secrecy of your password and user name. If you share a computer with anyone, you should always log out of your account after you are finished, in order to prevent access to your information from subsequent users of that computer. Please notify us as soon as possible if your user name or password is compromised.

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personally identifiable information, you acknowledge that: (a) there are security and privacy limitations of the Internet which are beyond our control; (b) the security, integrity and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and us through this RankStore cannot be guaranteed and we shall have no liability to you or any third party for loss, misuse, disclosure or alteration of such information; and (c) any such information and data may be viewed or tampered with in transit by a third party.

In the unlikely event that we believe that the security of your personally identifiable information in our control may have been compromised, we will notify you as promptly as possible under the circumstances. To the extent we have your e-mail address, we may notify you by e-mail and you consent to our use of email as a means of such notification.

**RankStore** does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this [website](http://www.rankstore.com/).

We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from **RankStore** by contacting us at our [website](http://www.rankstore.com/contact-us/ "Contact") or at our mailing address:

**New Developments, LLC**

333 NE 24th Street. Ste 209.

Miami, FL. 33137. USA

Email: alexa@rankstore.com

**RankStore** will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. **RankStore** encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how **RankStore** is protecting your information.

**RankStore** welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that **RankStore** has not adhered to this Statement, please contact **RankStore** at our [website](http://www.rankstore.com/contact-us/ "Contact") or at our mailing address:

**New Developments, LLC**

333 NE 24th Street. Ste 209.

Miami, FL. 33137. USA

Email: alexa@rankstore.com

Effective as of **November-20-** **2009**
